[{"prompt": "I became", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We became", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "X", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u0646", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) became", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) became", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "X", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062a"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) became", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"], [""], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "X", "_", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) became", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_letters": [], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) became", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They became", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "I might become", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0623"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0623", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "We might become", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0646"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0646", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(m) might become", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(f) might become", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) might become", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) might become", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u064a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) might become", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "They might become", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u064a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "I become", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We become", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u0646", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) become", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) become", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) become", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) becomes", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) becomes", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They become", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "I will become", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We will become", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u0646", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) will become", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) will become", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) will become", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) will become", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) will become", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They will become", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "You(m) become!", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0625", "\u064a"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "You(f) become!", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0625", "\u064a"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "You(pl) become!", "base_form": "\u0628\u0640\u064e\u0642\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0625", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "I were", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We were", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) were", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) were", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"], ["\u062a"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) were", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"], [""], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "I might be", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0623"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0623", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "We might be", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0646"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0646", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(m) might be", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(f) might be", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) might be", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) might be", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u064a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) might be", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "They might be", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u064a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "I be", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We be", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u0646", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) be", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) be", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) be", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) bes", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) bes", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They be", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "I will be", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We will be", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u0646", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) will be", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) will be", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) will be", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) will be", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) will be", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They will be", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "You(m) be!", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "You(f) be!", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u064a"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "You(pl) be!", "base_form": "\u0643\u0627 \u064e\u0646", "exercise_initial": [["\u0643"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0646"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0643"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "I began", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We began", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "X", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u0646", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) began", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) began", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "X", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062a"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) began", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"], [""], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "X", "_", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) began", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_letters": [], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) began", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They began", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "I might begin", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0623"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0623", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "We might begin", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0646"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0646", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(m) might begin", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(f) might begin", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) might begin", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) might begin", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u064a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) might begin", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "They might begin", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u064a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "I begin", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We begin", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u0646", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) begin", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) begin", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) begin", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) begins", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) begins", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They begin", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "I will begin", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We will begin", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u0646", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) will begin", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) will begin", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) will begin", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) will begin", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) will begin", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They will begin", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "You(m) begin!", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "You(f) begin!", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "You(pl) begin!", "base_form": "\u0625\u0628\u062a\u0640\u064e\u062f\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "I spoke", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We spoke", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0646", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) spoke", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) spoke", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], ["\u062a"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) spoke", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], [""], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) spoke", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_letters": [], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) spoke", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They spoke", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "I might speak", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0623"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0623"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "We might speak", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0646"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0646"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(m) might speak", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(f) might speak", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) might speak", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) might speak", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u064a"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) might speak", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "They might speak", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u064a"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "I speak", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We speak", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0646"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u0646"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) speak", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) speak", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) speak", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) speaks", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) speaks", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They speak", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "I will speak", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We will speak", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u0646"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u0646"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) will speak", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) will speak", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) will speak", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) will speak", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) will speak", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They will speak", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "You(m) speak!", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"]], "exercise_letters": [], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "You(f) speak!", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "You(pl) speak!", "base_form": "\u0625\u062a\u0643\u0640\u064e\u0644\u0651\u0640\u0650\u0645", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "I did", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We did", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0646", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) did", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) did", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], ["\u062a"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) did", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "_", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) did", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": [], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) did", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They did", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "I might do", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0623"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0623"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "We might do", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0646"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0646"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(m) might do", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(f) might do", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) might do", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) might do", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u064a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) might do", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "They might do", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u064a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "I do", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We do", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u0646"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) do", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) do", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) do", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) does", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) does", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They do", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "I will do", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We will do", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u0646"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) will do", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) will do", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) will do", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) will do", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) will do", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They will do", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "You(m) do!", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0625"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "You(f) do!", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0625", "\u064a"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "You(pl) do!", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u064e\u0645\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0625", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "I gave", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We gave", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "X", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u0646", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) gave", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) gave", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "X", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062a"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) gave", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"], [""], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "X", "_", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) gave", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_letters": [], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) gave", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They gave", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "We might give", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0646"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0646", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(m) might give", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(f) might give", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) might give", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) might give", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u064a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) might give", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "They might give", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u064a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "I give", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We give", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0646"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u0646", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) give", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) give", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) give", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) gives", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) gives", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They give", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "I will give", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We will give", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u0646"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u0646", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) will give", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) will give", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) will give", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) will give", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) will give", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They will give", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "You(m) give!", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "You(pl) give!", "base_form": "\u0625\u062f\u0651\u0649", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0649"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u062f"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) knew", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u0650\u0631 \u0650\u0641", "exercise_initial": [["\u0639"], ["\u0631"], ["\u0641"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0639"], ["\u0631"], ["\u0641"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They knew", "base_form": "\u0639\u0640\u0650\u0631 \u0650\u0641", "exercise_initial": [["\u0639"], ["\u0631"], ["\u0641"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0639"], ["\u0631"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "I lived", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We lived", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u0646", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) lived", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) lived", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) lived", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"], [""], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "I might live", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0623"], ["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0623", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "We might live", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0646"], ["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0646", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(m) might live", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(f) might live", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u064a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) might live", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) might live", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u064a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) might live", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "They might live", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u064a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "I live", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We live", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u0646", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) live", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) live", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u064a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) live", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) lives", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) lives", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They live", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "I will live", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We will live", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u0646", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) will live", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) will live", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u064a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) will live", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) will live", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) will live", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They will live", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "You(m) live!", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "You(f) live!", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u064a"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "You(pl) live!", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0634", "exercise_initial": [["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0634"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0639"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "I loved", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We loved", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], [""], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "_", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u0646", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) loved", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) loved", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], [""], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "_", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062a"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) loved", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], [""], [""], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "_", "_", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) loved", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_letters": [], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) loved", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They loved", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "I might love", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0623"], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0623"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "We might love", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0646"], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0646"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(m) might love", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(f) might love", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) might love", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) might love", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u064a"], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) might love", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "They might love", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u064a"], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "I love", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We love", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0646"], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u0646"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) love", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) love", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) love", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) loves", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) loves", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They love", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "I will love", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We will love", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u0646"], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u0646"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) will love", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) will love", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) will love", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) will love", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) will love", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They will love", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "You(m) love!", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062d"], ["\u0628"]], "exercise_letters": [], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "You(f) love!", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "You(pl) love!", "base_form": "\u062d\u0640\u064e\u0628\u0651", "exercise_initial": [["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062d"], ["\u0628"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "I said", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We said", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u0646", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) said", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) said", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"], ["\u062a"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) said", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "I might say", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0623"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0623", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "We might say", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0646"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0646", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(m) might say", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(f) might say", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) might say", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) might say", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u064a"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) might say", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "They might say", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u064a"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "I say", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We say", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u0646", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) say", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) say", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) say", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) says", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) says", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They say", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "I will say", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We will say", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u0646", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) will say", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) will say", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) will say", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) will say", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) will say", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They will say", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "You(m) say!", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "You(f) say!", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u064a"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "You(pl) say!", "base_form": "\u0642\u0627 \u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0642"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0642"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "I checked", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We checked", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u0646", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) checked", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) checked", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"], ["\u062a"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) checked", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"], [""], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "I might check", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0623"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0623", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "We might check", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0646"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0646", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(m) might check", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(f) might check", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) might check", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) might check", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u064a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) might check", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "They might check", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u064a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "I check", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We check", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u0646", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) check", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) check", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) check", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) checks", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) checks", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They check", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "I will check", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We will check", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u0646", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) will check", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) will check", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) will check", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) will check", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) will check", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They will check", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "You(m) check!", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "You(f) check!", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u064a"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "You(pl) check!", "base_form": "\u0634\u0627 \u064e\u0641", "exercise_initial": [["\u0634"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0641"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "I thought", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We thought", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0646", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) thought", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) thought", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], ["\u062a"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) thought", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], [""], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "_", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) thought", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_letters": [], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "They thought", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "I might think", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0623"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0623"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "We might think", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0646"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0646"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(m) might think", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(f) might think", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) might think", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) might think", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u064a"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) might think", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "They might think", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u064a"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "I think", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We think", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u0646"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) think", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) think", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) think", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) thinks", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) thinks", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They think", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "I will think", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We will think", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u0646"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) will think", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) will think", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) will think", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) will think", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) will think", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They will think", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "You(m) think!", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0625"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "You(f) think!", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0625", "\u064a"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "You(pl) think!", "base_form": "\u0641\u0640\u064e\u0643\u0651\u0640\u064e\u0631", "exercise_initial": [["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0641"], ["\u0643"], ["\u0631"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "I walked", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We walked", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0646", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) walked", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) walked", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062a"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) walked", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"], [""], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "_", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) walked", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": [], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) walked", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They walked", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "I might walk", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0623"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0623", "\u0649"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "We might walk", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0646"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0646", "\u0649"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(m) might walk", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0649"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(f) might walk", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) might walk", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) might walk", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u064a"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u0649"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) might walk", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0649"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "They might walk", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u064a"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "I walk", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u0649"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We walk", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u0646", "\u0649"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) walk", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u0649"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) walk", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) walk", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) walks", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a", "\u0649"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) walks", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u0649"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They walk", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "I will walk", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u0649"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We will walk", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u0646", "\u0649"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) will walk", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u0649"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) will walk", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) will walk", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) will walk", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a", "\u0649"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) will walk", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u0649"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They will walk", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "You(m) walk!", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "X"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0649"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0625", "\u0649"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "You(f) walk!", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0625"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "You(pl) walk!", "base_form": "\u0645\u0640\u0650\u0634\u064a", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u064a"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "O", "X", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0645"], ["\u0634"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0625", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "I wanted", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We wanted", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u0646", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) wanted", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) wanted", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"], ["\u062a"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) wanted", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"], [""], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "I might want", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0623"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0623", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "We might want", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0646"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0646", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(m) might want", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(f) might want", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) might want", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) might want", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u064a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) might want", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "They might want", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u064a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "I want", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We want", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u0646", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) want", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) want", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) want", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) wants", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) wants", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They want", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "I will want", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We will want", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u0646", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) will want", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) will want", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) will want", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) will want", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) will want", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u0648"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They will want", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [[""], [""], ["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "_", "O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "You(m) want!", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "You(f) want!", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u064a"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "You(pl) want!", "base_form": "\u0639\u0627 \u064e\u0632", "exercise_initial": [["\u0639"], ["\u0627"], ["\u0632"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "X", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0639"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0632"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "I worked", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We worked", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0646", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) worked", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) worked", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], ["\u062a"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) worked", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) worked", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": [], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) worked", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], ["\u062a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They worked", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "I might work", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0623"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0623"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "We might work", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0646"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0646"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(m) might work", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(f) might work", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) might work", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) might work", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u064a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) might work", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u062a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u062a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "They might work", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u064a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645 \u064a\u0645\u0643\u0646"}, {"prompt": "I work", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We work", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u0646"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) work", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) work", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) work", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) works", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) works", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They work", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0628"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0628", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "I will work", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647"], "intro": "\u0623\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "We will work", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u0646"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u0646"], "intro": "\u0625\u062d\u0646\u0627"}, {"prompt": "You(m) will work", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(f) will work", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a"}, {"prompt": "You(pl) will work", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0625\u0646\u062a\u0648\u0627"}, {"prompt": "He/it(m) will work", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a"], "intro": "\u0647\u0648"}, {"prompt": "She/it(f) will work", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u062a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u062a"], "intro": "\u0647\u064a"}, {"prompt": "They will work", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [[""], ["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["_", "X", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0647"], ["\u064a"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0647", "\u064a", "\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": "\u0647\u0645"}, {"prompt": "You(m) work!", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"]], "exercise_letters": [], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "You(f) work!", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], ["\u064a"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u064a"], "intro": ""}, {"prompt": "You(pl) work!", "base_form": "\u0625\u0634\u062a\u0640\u064e\u063a\u0640\u064e\u0644", "exercise_initial": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], [""], [""]], "exercise_template": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "_", "_"], "exercise_solution": [["\u0625"], ["\u0634"], ["\u062a"], ["\u063a"], ["\u0644"], ["\u0648"], ["\u0627"]], "exercise_letters": ["\u0648", "\u0627"], "intro": ""}]